CHRISTOPHER LEONARDO DE OLIVEIRA

- Av. Curitiba, Ernandes Gonçalves, Presidente Médici, Brazil
- ☑ christopherforwork@gmail.com
- **** +5569992029211
- https://christopherldo.github.io/
- https://github.com/christopherldo/

OBJECTIVE

I'm looking for full-time work in the role of Developer in the IT and telecommunications industry.

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Kia Ora! I am a young man who has so much to learn. Much to learn about English, about people, and, of course, about life. New Zealand is a great country to live in, and I am trying to reach back into this beautiful country. I am full of determination, full of charisma, and full of willingness to learn. I have many experiences in the programming area, and I am sure I will make you proud of me.

WORK HISTORY

Betabit Dev

Remote, Brazil Jun 2022 - Sep 2022

Zeroum Space

Remote, Brazil Jan 2022 - Jan 2023

SUTHUB

Remote, Brazil Nov 2021 - Jan 2022

Betabit Dev

Remote, Brazil Aug 2021 - Oct 2021

Software Developer

It was a full-time, remote job.

Stack: Next.js, Nest.js, React.js, TypeScript, PHP, JavaScript, MySQL.

Full Stack Developer

It was a partnership with a marketing company, where they got clients, and I developed mobile apps, web pages, and API services.

You can see some of them here:

- Prismapp:

https://www.prismapp.com.br/

- Cashback da Cidade:

https://cashbackdacidade.com.br/

- DriveCrypto:

https://drivecrypto.io/

Frontend Developer

It was a Vue.js, full-time job.

Stack: Vue.js, JavaScript, Node.js.

- Maintain and improve web pages
- Optimize applications for maximum velocity
- Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability
- Get feedback from, and build solutions for, users and customers

Web Developer

It was a full-time remote job I did when initiated at university.

Stack: React.js, Redux, PHP, JavaScript, Laravel.

- Make and maintain web pages
- Optimize performance and traffic capacity

Food on Q

Queenstown, New Zealand Feb 2020 - May 2020

OCS

Queenstown, New Zealand Dec 2019 - Jan 2020

RedeTV

Ji-Paraná, Brazil Feb 2017 - Jun 2017

Food Delivery Driver

This was a full-time job I did before the pandemic time.

- Deliver orders within an optimal period of time, ensuring freshness of food and respect for customer preferences
- Safely operate a vehicle in all types of weather conditions
- Navigate local streets and highways efficiently using GPS
- Communicate clearly with customers and food service employees, demonstrating an eagerness to work through any issues or points of confusion

Cleaner

This was a full-time job, my first full-time job, and my first job in New Zealand.

• Basic cleaning in office buildings

Video editor

This was the first part-time job I did to get some money and pay for my travels around the country.

 Editing and assembling recorded raw material into a suitable, finished product ready for broadcasting

QUALIFICATIONS

Universidade Cruzeiro do Sul

São Paulo, Brazil 2020 - Present

Jovem Gonçalves Vilela

Ji-Paraná, Brazil 2016

Bachelor of Computer Science

School Certificate

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Full Car Licence
- Problem-solving
- Experimentation
- Programming languages
- Information systems management
- TypeScript

- Full Motorcycle Licence
- Coding
- · Computer and technology knowledge
- Software development
- JavaScript

PERSONAL SKILLS

Communication

I speak with all the people and I have great charisma.

Teamwork

I think collaboration is the best form to make a product successful.

Thinking Skills

Efficiency is an important thing. I always think about how to make my job more comfortable without losing efficiency (or increasing it).

Resilience

"I am what I do". This phrase represents so much to me because people need to know how to divide things and not mix them. I know this, I am resilient.

Willingness to Learn

No one knows everything in this world, and because of it, I am a man full of willing to discover and know more about my job.

Technology Enthusiast

I enjoy using computers and electronic equipment. I am always willing to learn more about the ins and outs of a product.

Math affinity

I am very dedicated to my studies, which include math sometimes. And I always get so devoted to it.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Working Holiday Visa

2010

As a Brazilian, receiving this visa was such a prize. With it, I could finally know how New Zealand is a great place to live.

INTERESTS

• Know more about New Zealand culture.

• Plan and program mobile apps, web pages, and APIs.

REFEREES

Adilson Silva

Strategic Planning Junior Analyst - Embracon Administradora de Consórcio

**** +5511963384924